https://moores-glass.co.uk/privacy-policy-2/#cookies-policy

HomeProductsCathode Ray TubesHollow Cathode Envelopes & Graded SealsMulti-Pin BasesPH Electrode Glass BodiesPhoto Ionization Detector (PID Glass Bodies)Vacuum ViewportsPhotomultiplier EnvelopesGlass Condom MouldsMachines DepartmentAuto LathesLinksGalleryAbout UsQuality ControlFind UsAbout MooresContact UsBlog +44 (0)1932 222314 andrew@moores-glass.co.uk
Moores Glass
Moores GlassHomeProductsCathode Ray TubesHollow Cathode Envelopes & Graded SealsMulti-Pin BasesPH Electrode Glass BodiesPhoto Ionization Detector (PID Glass Bodies)Vacuum ViewportsPhotomultiplier EnvelopesGlass Condom MouldsMachines DepartmentAuto LathesLinksGalleryAbout UsQuality ControlFind UsAbout MooresContact UsBlogPrivacy Policy
WHAT IS THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR?This privacy policy is for this website moores-glass.co.uk and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.OUR WEBSITEThis website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.USE OF COOKIESThis website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer / device. This complies with recent legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer / device.Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computers hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information.Other cookies may be stored to your computers hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.CONTACT & COMMSUsers contacting this website and/or its owners do so at their own discretion and provide any such personal details requested at their own risk. Your personal information is kept private and stored securely until a time it is no longer required or has no use, as detailed in the Data Protection Act 1998. Every effort has been made to ensure a safe and secure form to email submission process but advise users using such form to email processes that they do so at their own risk.EXTERNAL LINKSAlthough this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website. The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts.SOCIAL MEDIACommunication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.
